Guide to the David Benjamin Mixner Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Writings, 1989-2003; Series IV
  - Books
    - Stranger Among Friends
      - Memos used for the book, 1992-1996 (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - Outline, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - Photographs [no actual photographs; materials regarding photographs], 1996 (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Publicity, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Research, 1994, undated (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - Reviews, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 23)
      - Shuster [Todd], 1994 (Box 58, Folder 24)
      - Titles, undated (Box 58, Folder 25)
      - Treatment[screenplay], undated (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Screenplays
    - Dunes at Overveen
      - Complete script [bound volume], 2003 January (Box 58, Folder 27)
      - General, 2000-2001 (Box 58, Folder 28)
      - Budget, undated (Box 58, Folder 29)
      - Casting, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 30)
      - Comments, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 31)
      - Dutch, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 32)
      - Memos, 2000-2001 (Box 58, Folder 33)
      - MTV award, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 34)
      - Shooting schedule, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - Fire in the Soul
      - Complete script [bound volume], undated (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Speeches, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 37)
- Clippings, 1968-2005; Series V
  The series is loosely arranged in chronological order.
  - 1960s-1980s (Box 59)
  - 1990s (Box 60–61)
  - 1995-2005 (Box 62)
  - 1960s-1990s
  - PRO Peace, 1985-1986 (Box 63)
- Audiovisual, 1924, 1964-2004; Series VI
  The series is arranged in three groups: photographs, audiotapes, and videotapes.
  - Photographs
    - 1924 [Benjamin Mixner on pony with his grandfather] (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - 1964-1965 [David Mixner] (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - 1966 [David Haynes, Amy, and Mixner at Arizona State University] (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - 1967 [March on Pentagon] (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - 1969
      - McGovern Commission (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Vietnam Moratorium (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - 1970
      - Barnes for Congress
        - Barnes, Craig (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - Mixner, Patsy and David, Denver (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Colorado Project/Common Cause [Paula Herzmark, Craig Barnes, John Gardener, Mixner; possibly 1971] (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Stonehenge [Rick Stearns and Bill Clinton] (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - 1971 [Mixner family] (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - 1978
      - "No on Six"
        - "Briggs Woman Lunch" [Mixner and Gayle Wilson] (Box 64, Folder 12)
        - Mixner (Box 64, Folder 13)
        - Mixner, Peter Scott, and Sally Fiske (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Puerto Vallarta, Mexico [Peter Scott, Mixner, Ray Hartman, Doug Chadwick] (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - Scott, Peter, birthday party [Shirley MacLaine, Mixner, David Schaar?] (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Scott, Peter, house [Mixner and Scott] (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Early 1980s
      - Clinton, William Jefferson, event at Peter Scott's home [Hillary Rodham Clinton, Mixner, and Bill Clinton] (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - Palm Springs
        - Mixner family (Box 64, Folder 19)
        - Mixner, Mary (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - 1980
      - Carter, Jimmy and Mixner (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - Unidentified (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Ca. 1980-1981
      - Annison, Patsy (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - 1981
      - Africa trip
        - General
          - Donkey in Egypt (Box 64, Folder 24)
          - Mixner and Calvin [Calver?] (Box 64, Folder 24)
          - Mixner in front of pyramids (Box 64, Folder 24)
          - Monkeys in Kenya (Box 64, Folder 24)
          - Rhinos in Tanzania (Box 64, Folder 24)
          - Tribesman in Tanzania (Box 64, Folder 24)
        - Egypt
          - Luxor (Box 64, Folder 25)
          - Nile River (Box 64, Folder 26)
          - Pyramids (Box 64, Folder 27)
          - Sadat reception [Mixner and Patsy Annison] (Box 64, Folder 28)
          - Wildlife (Box 64, Folder 29)
      - Scott, Peter, and Mixner at Mixner/Scott, Inc. (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - 1982
      - Bradley, Tom, with Mixner and Peter Scott (Box 64, Folder 31)
      - Municipal Elections Committee of Los Angeles [Mary Louise Oates and Sheldon Andelson] (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - 1982? [Family reunion, Palm Springs: Michael Annison, David Mixner, Melvin Mixner, Patsy Annison, Donna Mixner] (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - 1982-1984
      - Gary Hart Presidential Campaign
        - Democratic Convention in San Francisco [John Emerson, Mixner, Henry Waxman] (Box 64, Folder 34)
        - Hart Fundraiser at Sheldon Andelson's home [Gary Hart, Sheldon Andelson, Mixner] (Box 64, Folder 34)
        - Meeting in Mixner/Scott, Inc. offices [John Emerson, Jordon Mo, Gary Hart, Diane Abbitt, David Quarles] (Box 64, Folder 34)
        - Mixner at Democratic Convention (Box 64, Folder 34)
        - Mixner and Gary Hart (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - 1983
      - Mixner's 36th birthday party, Los Angeles
        - Mixner and Larry Irvin (Box 64, Folder 35)
        - Mixner, Louise, and Hart Lyon (Box 64, Folder 36)
        - Mixner with Jeff Applegate (Box 64, Folder 37)
        - Scott, Peter (Box 64, Folder 37)
        - Scott, Peter, with Roberta, Dianne, Mixner (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - 1984
      - Hart campaign in New York City [Larry Weghorst, Mixner] (Box 64, Folder 38)
      - 1984 Coalition in San Francisco (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - 1985
      - Annison, Julie with Frederico Peña and Elizabeth Annison (Box 64, Folder 40)
      - Mixner with Neal Tipton's dog (Box 64, Folder 41)
      - PRO Peace fundraiser in Laguna Beach [Chris Townsend, Mixner, David Stein] (Box 64, Folder 42)
    - Ca. 1985 [Geraldine at Cynthia Street] (Box 64, Folder 43)
    - 1985-1986
      - PRO Peace
        - Estevez, Emilio, with [Martha Plimpton], Lance Guest, Mixner, Demi Moore, Michael Nouri, Melissa Gilbert, and Rob Lowe (Box 64, Folder 44)
        - Havens, Richie, and Mixner (Box 64, Folder 44)
        - Hess, Alger, and Mixner (Box 64, Folder 44)
        - Madonna, Mixner, Rosanna Arquette (Box 64, Folder 44)
        - Newman, Paul, with Mixner and Sally Fields (Box 64, Folder 44)
        - Newman, Paul, with Mixner and Ted Turner (Box 64, Folder 44)
    - 1986
      - Family at Mary and Benjamin Mixner's Denver home
        - Annison, Elizabeth (Box 64, Folder 45)
        - Annison, Patsy and Michael (Box 64, Folder 45)
      - "No on 64" [Mixner and Torie Osborn] (Box 64, Folder 46 - 47)
      - PRO Peace march
        - Chavez, Cesar, and Mixner (Box 64, Folder 48)
        - Mixner (Box 64, Folder 49)
      - Tipton, Neal, and Mixner in Idyllwild, California (Box 64, Folder 50)
    - 1987
      - Coleman, Mark, in Canon Beach, Oregon (Box 64, Folder 51)
      - March on Washington
        - Mixner (Box 64, Folder 52)
        - Mixner, Tim Furlong, David Quarles, Roberta Bennett (Box 64, Folder 52)
        - General view (Box 64, Folder 52)
    - 1988
      - Coleman, Mark, in Hawaii (Box 64, Folder 53)
      - Dukakis [Michael] for President rally, University of California, Los Angeles [Jeff Gibson, Mixner] (Box 64, Folder 54)
      - "Neruda" [Mixner's Cynthia Street apartment, West Hollywood] (Box 64, Folder 55)
      - Quilt at University of California, Los Angeles [Julie and Elizabeth Annison] (Box 64, Folder 56)
    - 1989
      - Family [Julie and Elizabeth Annison school pictures] (Box 64, Folder 57)
      - Family reunion in Denver [Thanksgiving] (Box 64, Folder 58)
      - Mixner [head shots] (Box 64, Folder 59)
      - Laughlin, Bradley, with Mixner in Newport, Oregon (Box 64, Folder 60)
      - Press, Bill, and Mixner (Box 64, Folder 61)
      - Unidentified (Box 64, Folder 62)
    - 1990 [Bradley Laughlin and Mixner] (Box 64, Folder 63)
    - 1991
      - Hitt, Scott, and Alex Koleszar's 10th anniversary
        - General (Box 64, Folder 64)
        - Mixner and John Scott (Box 64, Folder 65)
        - Mixner and Alex Koleszar (Box 64, Folder 65)
        - Mixner, Alex Koleszar, Gilbert Calvillo, Scott Hitt (Box 64, Folder 65)
        - Mixner and Jeff Matchan (Box 64, Folder 65)
      - Kerrey, Robert, with Mixner (Box 64, Folder 66)
      - Mixner [head shots] (Box 64, Folder 67)
      - Sacramento rally (Box 64, Folder 68)
    - 1992
      - Achtenberg, Roberta, and Mixner (Box 64, Folder 69)
      - Arellanas, Art, and Mixner at Hollywood Palace (Box 64, Folder 70)
      - Bernard, Jeremy, with Mixner and John Garamendi (Box 64, Folder 71)
      - Bernard, Jeremy, with Mixner and Hillary Rodham Clinton [Clinton campaign] (Box 64, Folder 72)
      - Clinton, Hillary, with Mixner
        - AIDS Project/Los Angeles (Box 64, Folder 73)
        - Dinner (Box 64, Folder 74)
      - Clinton, William Jefferson
        - Clinton event [Mixner and Howard Bragman] (Box 64, Folder 75)
        - Clinton fundraisers
          - 1992 Feb, Beverly Wilshire
            - Achtenberg, Roberta, with Clinton, Mixner (Box 64, Folder 76)
            - Clinton and Mixner (Box 64, Folder 76)
            - Clinton, Mixner, Roberta Achtenberg (Box 64, Folder 76)
            - Clinton, Mixner, Roberta Achtenberg (Box 64, Folder 77)
            - Clinton, Mixner, Roberta Achtenberg (Box 64, Folder 77)
            - Mixner and Bob Sertner (Box 64, Folder 77)
            - Mixner and Jeremy Bernard (Box 64, Folder 77)
            - Mixner and Jim Neal (Box 64, Folder 77)
          - 1992 Apr [Hillary Rodham Clinton, Jeremy Bernard, Mixner] (Box 64, Folder 78)
          - 1992 Jun 18, San Fernando Valley [Mixner and Clinton] (Box 64, Folder 79)
        - Hollywood Palace
          - Clinton (Box 64, Folder 80 - 81)
          - Clinton speech [Mixner and Scott Hitt] (Box 64, Folder 82)
      - Democratic National Convention, New York City
        - Mixner (Box 64, Folder 83)
        - Mixner (Box 64, Folder 84)
        - Mixner, Bob Sertner, Charles Wang (Box 64, Folder 84)
        - Mixner, Chris Hershey, Diane Abbitt, Scott Hitt (Box 64, Folder 84)
        - Mixner, Diane Abbitt, Chris Hershey (Box 64, Folder 84)
        - Molleda, Nancy and Tom Henderson (Box 64, Folder 85)
      - Human Rights Campaign Fund dinner [Mixner, Chuck Holmes, and others] (Box 64, Folder 86)
      - Mixner [head shots-proof sheets] (Box 64, Folder 87)
      - Mixner and Jeremy Bernard (Box 64, Folder 88)
      - Paris (Box 64, Folder 89)
      - Prague [Terry Bean, Chuck Holmes, William Higgins, Mixner, and two unidentified] (Box 64, Folder 90)
      - Victory Fund, New York City (Box 64, Folder 91)
      - Weghorst, Larry (Box 64, Folder 92)
    - 1993
      - "Don't Ask, Don't Tell" (Box 64, Folder 93)
      - Gore, Albert, Jr. (Box 64, Folder 94)
      - Inauguration
        - Mixner and Roberta Achtenberg (Box 64, Folder 95)
        - Parade
          - Davis, David, with Tim Keely, Jeff Matchan, Mixner, [Carl Tubls?], Howard Bragman, David Kessler (Box 64, Folder 96)
          - Mixner with Clinton in background (Box 64, Folder 96)
        - Salute to David Mixner
          - Mixner and Peter Yarrow (Box 64, Folder 97)
          - Mixner and Roberta Achtenberg (Box 64, Folder 97)
          - Mixner speaking (Box 64, Folder 97)
          - Thorn, Tracy (Box 64, Folder 97)
        - Victory Fund event
          - Mixner and Roberta Achtenberg (Box 64, Folder 98)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 99)
      - March on Washington
        - Mixner, Steve [last name unidentified], Greg Plowe (Box 64, Folder 100)
        - Metropolitan Community Church service
          - Mixner (Box 64, Folder 101)
          - Perry, Troy
          - Perry, Troy and Mixner [speech against "Don't Ask, Don't Tell"] (Box 64, Folder 102)
          - Perry, Troy and Mixner (Box 64, Folder 103)
      - Victory Fund event [Lynn Greer and Mixner with their "Vicki's Awards"] (Box 64, Folder 104)
      - White House arrest [for "Don't Ask, Don't Tell" policy]
        - General (Box 64, Folder 105)
        - Training [Mel White, Jeff Matchan, Mixner] (Box 64, Folder 106)
        - Lobby of Four Seasons Hotel [Roberta Bennett, Mixner, John Duran, Tony Leonhardt, Diane Abbitt] (Box 64, Folder 106)
    - 1994
      - AIDS fundraiser in Washington, D.C. [Duane Rath, Mixner, Ted Hurdman, Mikhail Baryshnikov, Donna Shala, Jim Graham] (Box 64, Folder 107)
      - AIDS ride [Doug Lowery] (Box 64, Folder 108)
      - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AMFAR) event
        - Andelson, Arlan, with Mathilde Krim, Michelle Andelson presenting Mixner with "Sheldon Andelson Public Service Award" (Box 64, Folder 109)
        - Andelson, Arlan, with Michelle Andelson, Mathilde Krim, Mixner (Box 64, Folder 110)
        - Annison, Julie/Liz photographs [Mixner, Julie Annison, Elizabeth Annison] (Box 64, Folder 111)
        - Hormel, James, with Joel Weisman, Elizabeth Taylor, Clint Black, 2 unidentified, Mixner (Box 64, Folder 112)
        - Mixner (Box 64, Folder 113)
        - Mixner, Bob Hattoy, Michael Annison (Box 64, Folder 114)
        - Mixner, James Hormel, Joel Weisman (Box 64, Folder 115)
        - Mixner and Mathilde Krim (Box 64, Folder 116)
        - Mixner and Peter Anton (Box 64, Folder 117)
        - Proof sheets (Box 64, Folder 118)
        - Weisman, Joel, with Elizabeth Taylor, Clint Black, Mixner (Box 64, Folder 119)
      - Department of Justice [Kevin James and Attorney General Janet Reno] (Box 64, Folder 120)
      - Eisner, Michael, with Mixner, Clint Black (Box 64, Folder 121)
      - Family
        - Annison, Julie and Elizabeth school photographs (Box 64, Folder 122)
        - Family reunion [Melvin Mixner, David Mixner, Michael Annison, Julie Annison, Benjamin Mixner, Patsy Annison, Donna Mixner, Elizabeth Annison] (Box 64, Folder 123)
      - Gay Games, closing ceremony at Yankee Stadium [Mixner and Doug Lowery] (Box 64, Folder 124)
      - Lyndon Baines Johnson ranch [Doug Lowery, Mixner, Charles A. Robb, Lady Bird Johnson, Jeremy Bernard] (Box 64, Folder 125)
      - Prague [Chuck Holmes, Mixner, Terry Bean] (Box 64, Folder 126)
      - Richards, Anne and Mixner (Box 64, Folder 127)
      - Victory Fund event in New York City [Joy Tomchin and Mixner] (Box 64, Folder 128)
      - White House, California Day
        - Bernard, Jeremy, with Mixner, Steve Nuskiewicz (Box 64, Folder 129)
        - Lowery, Doug (Box 64, Folder 130)
        - Mixner and Roberta Bennett (Box 64, Folder 131)
    - 1995
      - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AMFAR) dinner in Beverly Hills
        - Mixner, Nancy Daly, Maya Riordan (Box 64, Folder 132)
        - Mixner introducing Jane Nathanson (Box 64, Folder 132)
      - "Blue glove incident," at the White House [Mixner, Chuck Holmes, Danny Seabright, George [last name unidentified], Ken Rugbush, Ayse Kenmore] (Box 64, Folder 133)
      - Clinton, William Jefferson and Hillary Rodham with Mixner (Box 64, Folder 134)
      - Clinton, William Jefferson and Patsy Annison in Denver, Colorado (Box 64, Folder 135)
      - Unidentified (Box 64, Folder 136)
    - 1996
      - American Booksellers Convention (Box 64, Folder 137)
      - Amsterdam [Mixner and Patrick Marston] (Box 64, Folder 138)
      - Gay Pride, Myrtle Beach (Box 64, Folder 139)
      - Holocaust Museum event for Gay and Lesbian Campaign and Duane Rath Endowment Fund (Box 64, Folder 140)
      - Mixner, David
        - Book parties
          - Annisons (Box 64, Folder 141)
          - Oates, Mary Louise, at Lynne Wasserman home [Patrick Marston, Mixner, Lynne Wasserman, Mary Louise Oates] (Box 64, Folder 142)
        - 50th birthday party, Fire Island (Box 64, Folder 143)
    - 1997
      - Annison, Julia, debutant weekend (Box 64, Folder 144)
      - Atlanta (Box 64, Folder 145)
      - Niece's wedding (Box 64, Folder 146)
      - Reyes, Andrew, and Mixner (Box 64, Folder 147)
    - 1998 [Denny Maust, Mixner, Kevin Terrell in Dallas, Texas] (Box 64, Folder 148)
    - 1999
      - Alaska cruise
        - General (Box 64, Folder 149)
        - Hubbard Glacier (Box 64, Folder 150)
      - Baldwin, Tammy, event
        - Mixner, Baldwin, Van Fletcher (Box 64, Folder 151)
        - Mixner and Gil Garcetti (Box 64, Folder 151)
        - Mixner, Gil Garcetti, Patrick Kennedy (Box 64, Folder 151)
        - Mixner, Van Fletcher, Skip Paul (Box 64, Folder 151)
      - Family reunion (Box 64, Folder 152)
      - Gray, Don, and Mixner at Mark's, Los Angeles (Box 64, Folder 153)
      - Lammie's (Box 64, Folder 154)
      - Presidential dinner, Oct [Mixner, Patsy Annison, Julia Annison, Elizabeth Annison, Tanner?] (Box 64, Folder 155)
      - Presidential dinner, Nov (Box 64, Folder 156)
      - White House [Mixner, Jane Nathanson, Jeremy Bernard] (Box 64, Folder 157)
    - 2000
      - Africa (Box 64, Folder 158)
      - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AMFAR), Ellis Island event [Melamed? and Mixner] (Box 64, Folder 159)
      - Belcher, Vaughan [?] (Box 64, Folder 160)
      - Clinton, William Jefferson and Gray Davis (Box 64, Folder 161)
      - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee (DSCC) dinner (Box 64, Folder 162)
      - Family reunion (Box 64, Folder 163)
      - Hale House Awards (Box 64, Folder 164)
      - Mixner, David
        - Annison, Elizabeth, graduation (Box 64, Folder 165)
        - Birthday event (Box 64, Folder 166)
        - Book party (Box 64, Folder 167)
      - Victory Fund event, Mixner birthday, convention week (Box 64, Folder 168)
      - White House Christmas party (Box 64, Folder 169)
    - 2001
      - Amsterdam [Patrick Marston, Jim Baker, Glen Thomas, Ted Gaultier, Craig Bugbee, Randy McDowell] (Box 64, Folder 170)
      - King Mswati III (King of Swaziland), Regency Club, Los Angeles (Box 64, Folder 171)
      - Las Vegas (Box 64, Folder 172)
      - Mixner, David [receiving Dr. King Award, West Hollywood] (Box 64, Folder 173)
    - 2003 [Transatlantic Partnership Against AIDS] (Box 64, Folder 174)
    - 2004
      - Kaz, Dave (Box 64, Folder 175)
      - Kennedy, Edward, fundraising event for senators opposed to the Constitutional Amendment on Marriage
        - Compact disc [containing images; original compact disc; restricted] (Box 65)
        - Contact sheet and correspondence (Box 66, Folder 176)
      - Mixner, David (Box 66, Folder 177)
    - Various dates
      - C.M.S. Event
        - Mixner and Mark Goldberg, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 178)
        - Mixner and Alan Donius, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 178)
        - Mixner, Chris Hershey, Susan Van Horn, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 178)
      - Hershey, Chris, and Bill Clinton, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 178)
      - Annison, Patsy, with deer, undated (Box 66, Folder 179)
      - Mixner, Bob Parris, Rob Jackon, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 179)
      - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF) dinner [Jackie Goldberg and Mixner], 1995 (Box 66, Folder 179)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 66, Folder 179)
      - Prague [Chuck Holmes, Terry Bean, Mixner], 1994 (Box 66, Folder 180)
      - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AMFAR) dinner [Mixner with cowboy hat], undated (Box 66, Folder 180)
      - Victory Fund, New York City reception [Joe Steffin, Joy Tomchin, Mixner], 1995 (Box 66, Folder 180)
      - White House [Doug Lowery and Mixner], 1994 (Box 66, Folder 180)
    - Undated
      - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AMFAR) dinner
        - Mixner, James Hormel, Joel Weissman, Elizabeth Taylor, Clint Black, two unidentified (Box 66, Folder 181)
        - Mixner, Richard Riordan, Greg Louganis (Box 66, Folder 181)
      - Access Now for Gay and Lesbian Equality (ANGLE) breakfast for Al Checchi (Box 66, Folder 182)
      - Amsterdam [historical shots for Willem Arondeus] (Box 66, Folder 183)
      - Annison, Julia, birthday party at Jeremy Bernard's (Box 66, Folder 184)
      - Annison, Patsy, and Bill Clinton (Box 66, Folder 185)
      - Arizona State University [Kit] (Box 66, Folder 186)
      - Bennett, Roberta, and Mixner (Box 66, Folder 187)
      - Bernard, Jeremy, 35th birthday party [Mixner, Stuart Stone, George Mariella] (Box 66, Folder 188)
      - Bohnett, David event [Bohnett and Mixner] (Box 66, Folder 189)
      - Clinton, Hillary Rodham, event (Box 66, Folder 190)
      - Costanza, Midge, and Mixner (Box 66, Folder 191)
      - Democratic National Convention [Texas delegation: Nancy Moleda and Tom Henderson] (Box 66, Folder 192)
      - Family
        - Mixner, Benjamin (Box 66, Folder 193 - 194)
        - Mixner, John, with Albert Mixner, Benjamin Mixner (Box 66, Folder 195)
        - Mixner, Mary (Box 66, Folder 196)
        - Thanksgiving family photo [Annison home, Denver, Colorado] (Box 66, Folder 197)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 66, Folder 198)
      - Garamendi, John, and Mixner (Box 66, Folder 199)
      - Gephardt, Richard
        - Gephardt watched by Kevin James, Dan Baker, Mixner, Scott Hitt, Jack [Volarti?] (Box 66, Folder 200)
        - Mixner introducing Gephardt at fundraiser (Box 66, Folder 200)
      - Hitt, Scott, and Alex Koleszar (Box 66, Folder 201)
      - Holmes, Chuck, and Mixner (Box 66, Folder 202 - 203)
      - Kennedy, Edward, and Peter Scott (Box 66, Folder 204)
      - Kerry, John, with Chris Townsend, Mixner (Box 66, Folder 205)
      - Laughlin, Bradley (Box 66, Folder 206)
      - Marcus, Jeffrey (Box 66, Folder 207)
      - Mark's event [Mike Bento and Miller Brewing] (Box 66, Folder 208)
      - Martha's Vineyard (Box 66, Folder 209)
      - Milwaukee Victory Fund dinner with porn star (Box 66, Folder 210)
      - Mixner, David
        - Birthday party at Patsy's (Box 66, Folder 211)
        - Campaigning (Box 66, Folder 212)
      - Municipal Elections Committee of Los Angeles [Roberta Bennett, Mixner, Diane Abbitt] (Box 66, Folder 213)
      - National Quilt Weekend dinner [Patrick Marston and Mixner] (Box 66, Folder 214)
      - Noble, Elaine, and Mixner (Box 66, Folder 215)
      - Oates, Mary Louise (Box 66, Folder 216)
      - Sacramento protest (Box 66, Folder 217)
      - Scott, Peter (Box 66, Folder 218)
      - Smith, Robyn (Box 66, Folder 219)
      - Stranger Among Friends layout photos (Box 66, Folder 220)
      - White House "California Day" [Susan Van Horn, Mixner, Chris Hershey] (Box 66, Folder 221)
      - Unidentified (Box 66, Folder 222)
  - Audiotapes
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
    - Brave Journeys [interviews with: Roberta Achtenberg, Terry Anderson, Michael Begland, Michael Cashman, Dianne Hardy-Garcia, Rachelle Horowitz, Jim Kepner, Phillis Lyon, Sir Ian McKellen, Del Martin, Armistad Maupin, Glen Maxey, Nancy Molleda, Bettie Naylor, Lisa Power, Douglas Slater, Tracy Thorne, and William Waybourn], 29 audiocassettes, 1988, 1997-1999, undated (Box 67)
    - Gay.com
      - Cohen, Bruce, 2000 October 17; 1 (Box 68)
      - Gephardt, Richard, 2000 November 15; audiocassette (Box 68)
      - Kennedy, Edward, 2001 March 18; 1 (Box 68)
      - Light, Judith, 2001 March 1; 1 (Box 68)
      - Osborn, Torie, 2000 October 20; 1 (Box 68)
      - Pallone, David, 2001 March 8; 1 (Box 68)
      - Stephanopoulos, George, 2001 January 10; audiocassette (Box 68)
    - Other [interviews with or recordings of: Bill Angelos, Andrew Berrar, Jonathan Brice, Ernest Bromley, Chris Bull, Stephen G. Cary, Leonard DePaur, James R. Dumpson, William B. Edgerton, Larry Gara, Edward P. Gottlieb, Gravity, Nat Hentoff, Norman Hill, George Houser, Housing and Urban Development interviews, Gregg King, John Lewis, John McCartney, Tim McFeely, David McReynolds, Walter Naegle, Elaine Noble, Pro-Peace, Richard Ravitch, Bayard Rustin, David Smith, Todd Suko, Bento Trammell, George Williams], 25 audiocassettes, 1987-1997, undated (Box 69)
  - Videotapes
    - Personal